<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="4"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[Dear Fellow Owners of PFCU:We are having a fruitful year at Platinum Federal Credit Union (PFCU). Membership, Deposit, Loan, Account and Net Worth growth all have been moving in the right direction. Thanks to the participation from existing as well as new members. We want our members/owners to be the ambassadors of the credit union justlike the board and committee members and encourage your friends and family members of the community to consider PFCU  rst for deposits, loans, identity security and other  nancial products and services. Due to the positive growth, the board has decided to increase the dividend on share/ savings account to up to 0.50% from 0.30%.PFCU launched its 5th virtual branch outside Georgia in NY/ NJ. The launch was well received by the members of our community in NY/NJ. We would like to thank the National and NE EPB as well as the NE council for their support and help to create awareness of the products and services offered by PFCU to community members in the NE Region.Platinum Secure Checking is getting more attention from membership. We introduced this product in NY/NJ virtual branch and one of the Jamati members said, “I would become a member just to avail this product from PFCU”. We hope members open their checking accounts with PFCU and avail the bene ts of Secure Checking that has been offered toour members at subsidized cost. Please contact our member services representatives at 404-297-9797 to learn more about this product or visit our website.PFCU’s all new education portal is also gaining traction. We are seeing lot of traf c to these modules ranging from under- standing credit bureau FICO scores to retirement planning for individuals and from business savings to creating a business plan for business members. We encourage members to take advantage of this valuable no charge resource by visiting www.platinumfcu.org or www.Platinum.CreditUnion.PFCU is running a special on CDs with rates of 2.25% for a 13 month CD with no early withdrawal penalty and a minimum deposit as little as $1,000 in new money. You can also lock in for a longer term of 38 months at 2.75% with a one step up option during the life of the CD. We encourage members to take advantage of these specials.I would like to once again appeal to the members of Platinum Federal Credit Union to be the ambassadors and spread the word of the products and services offered by PFCU. With your participation and our staff and volunteers’ hard work we can keep achieving milestones and help more members of our community.Sincerely,Rahim AsaniRahim Asani Chairman]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[LAUNCH YOUR BUSINESS WITH RATES AS LOW AS 9.99% APR*Boost your business buying power with the Platinum FCU Small Business MasterCard® Credit Card, accepted everywhere you see the MasterCard symbol! Enjoy convenience, security and up to 1% Cash Back on all business purchases.VISIT ONE OF OUR CONVENIENT BRANCH LOCATIONS OR APPLY ONLINE TODAY!*Annual Percentage Rate.See credit union for more information.]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[FIND YOUR PLATINUM LINING IN CREDIT UNIONS!In honor of the 70th year of International Credit Union Day, and in recognition of the credit union difference, we invite you to  nd your platinum lining in credit unions!Over 235 million people choose credit union membership because of our “people- rst” philosophy. We strive to make the world a better placefor you by offering affordable rates and high quality service that simpli es your life and empowers you to meet your  nancial goals. But this is only part of the credit union difference. There are numerous differences (or platinum linings) that credit unions make for our members!• Not-for-pro t. We exist to serve you, not make a pro t. Earnings are returned to members through lower loan rates, higher interest on deposits, and lower fees.• Ownership. Each member has equal ownership and one vote -- regardless of how much money you have on deposit.• Volunteer Boards. Each credit union is governed by a voluntary board of directors, elected by and from the credit union’s membership.• Membership Eligibility. Credit unions cannot serve the general public. People qualify for membership through their employer, organizational af liations or place of residence.• Financial Education for Members. Credit unions assist members to become better- educated consumers of  nancial services.• Social Purpose: People Helping People. Credit unions exist to help people, not make a pro t. Our goal is to serve all of our members well, including those of modest means.On October 18, 2018, we will join more than 68,000 credit unions from 109 countries and their 235 million members to celebrate the 70th International Credit Union Day®. Please stop by the credit union on this day to help us celebrate all of the platinum linings credit union membership brings!1-877-PFCU4YOU (732-8496) www.platinumfcu.org Info@platinumfcu.orgBoard of DirectorsRahim Asani ChairmanNooruddin Mithani Vice ChairmanAmin Premjee SecretaryFazal Manji TreasurerAli Jamal Director - HRKarim KaisaniDirector – Supervisory CommitteeAmyn Abdulla Director – MarketingMushtaq Kamruddin Director – RecoveryMoyees Merchant Director – OutreachHoliday Closings Columbus DayMonday, October 8Veterans Day (Observed)Monday, November 12Thanksgiving DayThursday, November 22Christmas DayTuesday, December 25New Year’s DayTuesday, January 1We have more than 5,000 shared branch locations. Call us or visit our website to  nd one near youFederally insured by NCUAMembers have saved nearly $2 billion with Love My Credit Union® Rewards!Get more from your credit union membership at LoveMyCreditUnion.orgAssets: Loans: Members:August 2018$101,218,652 $79,460,475 9,039May 2018$100,512,221 $77,432,859 8,880February 2018$98,365,062 $72,977,254 8,731November 2017$94,162,952 $70,452,786 8,637]]></page></pages></Search>