<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="4"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[*Subject to credit approval. Rates and terms subject to change without notice. See credit union for full details. PFCU business loan eligibility requires business membership and the establishment of the par value of one share in a business savings account.Dear Fellow Members,The third quarter of 2017 continues with PFCU crossing new milestones re ecting steady growth. Assets passed the $100 Mil- lion mark for the  rst time for a day on Au- gust 7th. Our membership has reached 8,543, with outstanding loans and credit cards amounting to $68+ Million. I also want to thank the members that have taken ad-vantage of the Diamond Jubilee savings accounts program, which has taken off well at this early stage. For those not yet participating, it’s never too late.PFCU’s services also advance forward matching the growth with a new Online Banking Platform launching soon. Also, due to the growth and changes in regulations, the Personal, Signature and Business loan limits have been increased from $50,000 to $100,000.Many members are downloading and utilizing the latest mobile app 3.0 and utilizing its friendly navigation and features such as mobile check deposit. And it’s not only the Millennial members using these!The series of education and information sessions continue with an upcoming one on reducing the tax burden via 401K and the new landscape of medical coverage for small business owners. Mark your calendars for Wednesday, October 18th and make sure to pass this message on to your friends. See details on next page.Don’t forget, you can use the website www.platinumfcu.org to ac- cess the online member application, loan application and home mortgage application, as well as information on products and ser- vices, including our current specials. You will also  nd the ‘resources’ section useful, as it contains information and links on subjects such as fraud protection and cyber security.The Members of the Board of Directors and Committees, the Man- agement and the Staff join me in thanking the member owners for the tremendous support that has resulted in the growth and health of PFCU. Also, I was pleased to see our contingent joining proud- ly in support of the AKF Partnership Walk on September 17, 2017 at Stone Mountain Park.Sincerely, Kas Jinnah Chairman]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[SMALL BUSINESSSEMINAR ON SMALL BUSINESS TAX SAVINGS & MEDICAL COVERAGETOPICS COVERED:1. Signi cantly reduce your tax burden with a 401k or Cash Balance Plan 2. New landscape for medical coverage for small business owners3. Group Bene ts – tax savings strategy for small businessWHEN:Wednesday, October 18, 2017 @ 6:00 pmWHERE:Atlanta Retailers Association Training Room 2055 N. Brown Road. Lawrenceville, GA 30043]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[Platinum FCU has increased our limits on Personal, Signature & BusinessLoans*! Borrow up to $100,000** to help you reach your dreams. Whether you’re saving for a dream wedding, facing unexpected expenses, consolidating high interest debt, starting a new business or offsetting businesscosts, PFCU has a  exible loan to help, with rates as low as 6.99% APR***.Visit www.platinumfcu.org or one of our branch locations to apply today!*Loans subject to credit approval. Restrictions apply. See credit union for more detail. | **Maximums based on member credit standing. | *** Annual Percentage Rate]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[Your one-stop shop for affordable financial solutions!One-Stop ShopEverything you need to manage your  nances, all in one place.www.platinumfcu.orgPFCU Election Watch!1-877-PFCU4YOU (732-8496) www.platinumfcu.org Info@platinumfcu.orgBoard of DirectorsCSAIBTNMCOEULEBNATNMSKEIRGITNAERNOEKassemali JinnahILBANNKIONChairmanGEbrahim JafferHHCSS/SOLAARRNESDHBAIPRSORNEELPCCONTANLA/HBIEURNDSUGINUSETNSCISSLOASSATTMEM/CNTASSEHVNISNTNBNSUNOAVICNAGSSSBESNISUCAHEOCKLINOATUAGDCRDEIRCTSNAODLEIETCAMOGADGRTRPlatinum Federal Credit Union is soliciting members to be elected to the PFCU Board of Directors for 2018 – 2021. We would like to request members who have  nancial exper- tise, banking experience or other core skills to please call the Nominating Committee Chairman, Mr. Karim Kaisani at (404) 787-2536 or email KarimK@PlatinumFCU.org.Quali ed members can run for election as part of the nomination slate or can submit a petition signed by 1% of the membership (i.e. 85 mem- bers of Platinum Federal Credit Union). Inter- ested members should submit their completedapplication (available at the credit union), state- ment of quali cations and biographical data to:Platinum Federal Credit UnionAttn: Nominating Committee Chairman 2035 Sugarloaf ParkwayDuluth, GA 30097All applications must be submitted no later than December 15, 2017.Applicants should obtain the requirements of the position and other details from the credit union of ce.Mustaq Kamruddin Director - RecoveryHoliday Closings Columbus DayMonday, October 9Veterans Day (Observed)Friday, November 10Thanksgiving DayThursday, November 23Christmas DayMonday, December 25New Year’s DayMonday, January 1Assets: Loans: Members:August 2017$93,108,747 $68,225,298 8,543May 2017$91,569,815 $65,801,257 8,376February 2017$83,495,205 $62,575,873 8,190November 2016$82,422,565 $58,744,399 8,047We have more than 5,000 shared branch locations. Call us or visit our website to  nd one near youFederally insured by NCUAVice ChairmanNooruddin MithaniSecretaryFazal ManjiTreasurerRahim AsaniDirector Loan CommitteeAli JamalDirector - HRKarim KaisaniDirector - Supervisory CommitteeAmyn AbdullaDirector – Business Outreach]]></page></pages></Search>