<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="4"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[Dear Fellow Owners of PFCU:On behalf of the Board, committees and team members of Platinum Fed- eral Credit Union (PFCU), I would like to wish every member Imamat Day Mubarak. I would also like to takethis opportunity to thank members of PFCU and the board to put their trust and faith in me to lead this institution.I remember ex-Chairman Kas Jinnah had mentioned in his note in March 2014 that PFCU has crossed $50 million in assets and today I am proud to inform the members that PFCU has crossed $100 million in assets. With the help and support ofall of our members as well as the staff and volunteers we have been able to double the size of the credit union in just 4 years.Platinum Secure Checking went live on April 1st and we are seeing members taking advantage of the credit monitoring and identity theft protection as well as the cell phone insur- ance, prescription discount and various other services that are bundled in this product. We encourage members to fully uti- lize this service that has been offered to PFCU members at a subsidized cost. Please contact our member services repre- sentatives at 404-297-9797 to learn more about this product or visit our website at www.Platinum.CreditUnion.I would like to once again Congratulate the members of Platinum Federal Credit Union for crossing the $100 million mark in total assets and crossing the $75 million mark in total outstanding loans. With your participation and our staff and volunteers hard work we can keep achieving these milestones and help more members of our community.Sincerely,Rahim AsaniRahim Asani ChairmanWe had more than 400 members attend the 18th Annual Meeting where our Credit Union CEO Kabir Laiwalla informed members of the initiatives taken in the year 2017 and some of the plans for the year 2018. Ex-Chairman Kas Jinnah also updated the members about the fast-paced growth of PFCU and the technological enhancements in mobile and online banking. Southeast Council President Murad Abdulla shared some initiatives of the Institutions and the visit of our beloved Hazar Imam to Atlanta, Georgia.PFCU’s 2018 Scholarship Program Awards were given at the Annual meeting where with the support of Atlanta Retailers Association and other members of PFCU, we were able to award 42 scholarships of $2,500 each totaling to $105,000. We are proud of this program and we are working hard to keep enhancing and increasing this program to bene t more students of our community that have shown excellence in their education and extra-curricular activities.I am proud to inform the members that PFCU has launched education portal on its website to promote learning at your convenience. Members can access various modules ranging from understanding credit bureau FICO scores to retirement planning for individuals and from business savings to creating a business plan for business members. We encourage members to take advantage of this valuable no charge resource by visiting www.platinumfcu.org or www.Platinum.CreditUnion.]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[The 2018 Annual Meeting & Scholarship Award Ceremony was a great success!SE Council President Murad AbdullaEmployees of the Year 2017Scholarship Award RecipientsScholarship ContributorsRetiring Director Ebrahim JafferRetiring Director Kas JinnahMembers from all over came and enjoyed the meeting!]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[For the month of July enjoyNO PAYMENTS FOR 90 DAYS!Auto loans as low as 2.24% APR • Signature Loans as low as 6.99% APR Personal Loans as low as 6.99% APR • Business Loans as low as 7.99% APR Home Equity Loans as low as Prime • Student Deferred Loans as low as 5.99% APRACT FAST, THESE GREAT OFFERS ARE ONLY AVAILABLE FOR THE MONTH OF JULY.*All loans subject to credit approval.90 Day deferred applicable to new auto and personal loans only. Existing loans not eligible. Interest will continue to accrue, and deferment of payment will extend the life of the loan. Restrictions apply.See credit union for details. **Annual Percentage RateApply today online atplatinumfcu.org or visit one of our convenient branch locations!]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[Leaving for college is stressful enough. Platinum FCU makes the transition simple with our Student Package including:• Student Checking Accounts • Student Credit Cards• Student LoansLoans subject to credit approval. Restrictions apply. See credit union for full detail.Pla num Federal Credit Union Members Get Exclusive Discounts from Love My Credit Union RewardsEveryone loves to save, especially on products and services you use every day. That’s what Love My Credit Union Rewards is all about. Members have saved nearly $2 billion in discounts from valued partners through Love My Credit Union Rewards. You can save too with valuable discounts from these partners:♥ Get a $100 cash reward for each new line you ac vate, up to 3 lines. Plus, get a $50 cash reward every year for as long as you are a Sprint customer.*♥ Save up to $15 on TurboTax federal products!♥ Get an exclusive smoke communicator and a $100 gi  card with a new ADT monitoredhome security system. Call 844-703-0123 to ac vate this special o er.♥ Get trusted protec on at true savings with the TruStage Auto & Home Insurance Program.♥ Shop and get cash back at over 1,500 online retailers with Love to Shop.To  nd out more and learn about other valuable discounts, www.Pla num.CreditUnion or LoveMyCreditUnion.org. You get all these o ers and discounts just for being a member of Pla num Federal Credit Union.*Limited  me o ers. Ac v. Fee: Up to $30/line. Credit approval req. Cash Reward O ers: Avail. for eligible credit union members & member employees with qualifying corp. id. (ongoing veri ca on). $100 Cash Reward for new smartphone line ac v. up to 3 lines. Req. ac v. at point of sale. Excludes CL, MBB devices, tablets, Sprint Phone Connect, upgrs., replacements & ports made between Sprint en  es or providers associated with Sprint. Limit one SWP Corp ID per Sprint acct. No add’l. discounts apply. Loyalty Reward: $50/line/yr. Cash Reward up to 3 lines when Sprint acct. remains ac ve and in good standing each yr. Transfer Reward: Members par cipa ng in another discount program are eligible for a $50 Cash Reward for up to 3 smartphone lines transferred to Cash Reward program. Deposit: Cash Reward issued by CU Solu ons Group. Sprint acct. must remain ac ve and in good standing for 31 days to receive Cash Reward. Allow 6-8 wks. for Cash Reward to be deposited to your Credit Union acct. If the Cash Reward does not appear a er 8 wks., visit lovemycreditunion.org/sprintrewards & click on “Cash Rewards Tracker”. Other Terms: O er/coverage not avail. everywhere or for all phones/networks. May not be combinable with other o ers. O er, terms, restric ons, & op ons subject to change & may be modi ed, discon nued, or terminated at any  me without no ce. Restric ons apply. © 2018 Sprint. All rights reserved. Sprint & the logo are trademarks of Sprint. Other marks are the property of their respec ve owners.1-877-PFCU4YOU (732-8496) www.platinumfcu.org Info@platinumfcu.orgBoard of DirectorsRahim Asani ChairmanNooruddin Mithani Vice ChairmanAmin Premjee SecretaryFazal Manji TreasurerAli Jamal Director - HRKarim KaisaniDirector – Supervisory CommitteeAmyn Abdulla Director – MarketingMushtaq Kamruddin Director – RecoveryMoyees Merchant Director – OutreachHoliday Closings Independence DayWednesday, July 4, 2018Imamat Day(Closing One Hour Early) Wednesday, July 11, 2018Labor DayMonday, September 3, 2018We have more than 5,000 shared branch locations. Call us or visit our website to  nd one near youFederally insured by NCUAAssets: Loans: Members:May 2018$100,512,221 $77,432,859 8,880February 2018$98,365,062 $72,977,254 8,731November 2017$94,162,952 $70,452,786 8,637August 2017$93,108,747 $68,225,298 8,543]]></page></pages></Search>