<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="6"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Dear Members,
On behalf of the Board, commit- tees and team members of Plati- num Federal Credit Union (PFCU), I would like to wish Imamat Day Mubarak. I would also like to
take this opportunity to welcome
our new Board of Directors Mrs. Shereza Tajuddin, Mrs. Shahina Punjani and Mr. Man-
soor Wadsariya.
Our 19th Annual Meeting was attended by 500 mem- bers. During the meeting PFCU CEO, Kabir Laiwal-
la informed members of the initiatives taken by PFCU during 2018. I reviewed updates on our continued phe- nomenal growth and how we are keeping up with the banking industry. Southeast Council President Murad Abdulla shared the importance of savings and passing the wealth to not only the next generation but multiple generations. U. S. Representative Rob Woodall shared some key highlights of PFCU performance compared to other credit union’s its size. Representative Wood- all complimented the efforts of PFCU especially the low delinquency, low charge offs and positive overall growth.
During the annual meeting we also awarded 40 schol- arships of $2,500 each totaling to $100,000 with PFCU’s 2019 Scholarship Program. This program is supported by PFCU, Atlanta Retailers Association, other Trade as- sociations and several members of PFCU. We appreci- ate the support of our sponsors in the scholarships pro- gram. With more sponsors we can continue enhancing and increasing benefits to more students of our com- munity that have shown excellence in their education and extra-curricular activities.
Last year we launched the Platinum Secure Checking account that provides members with several benefits
including but not limited to credit monitoring, identi- ty theft protection, cell phone insurance, prescription discount, etc. We encourage members to fully utilize this service that has been offered to PFCU members at a highly subsidized cost. Please contact our member services representatives at 404-297-9797 to learn more about this product or visit our website at www.platinumfcu.org or www.Platinum.CreditUnion.
We are running specials on Auto and Home Mortgage loans and encourage members to take advantage of the same. For Home Mortgage PFCU has launched a new program for non-jumbo loans with ZERO origina- tion Fees, ZERO intangible taxes, PLUS contributing $500 towards closing costs for a limited time. So, con- tact PFCU Loan Officers to finance or refinance your mortgage loans this summer with PFCU.
As members are aware that PFCU launched education portal on its website to promote learning at your con- venience. Members can access various modules rang- ing from understanding credit bureau FICO scores
to retirement planning for individuals and from busi- ness savings to creating a business plan for business members. We encourage members to take advantage of this valuable no charge resource by visiting www.platinumfcu.org or www.Platinum.CreditUnion.
With your participation and our staff and volunteers hard work we can keep achieving these milestones and help more members of our community.
Sincerely,
Rahim Asani
Rahim Asani Chairman
]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Let PFCU help you fund your next
           Whether you’re looking for a first home, newer home or vacation home, Platinum FCU can help with a low rate mortgage*! We have fixed rates with terms of 10, 15, 20 and 30 years as well as FHA loans, VA loans and Adjust- able Rate Mortgages (ARMs).
PLUS, we offer:
• ZERO Origination Fees**
• ZERO Intangible Taxes
• $500 Towards Closing Costs***!
Your next home just got that much sweeter! Apply now to get started on your next home sweet home.
NMLS#609086
*All loans subject to credit approval. Some restrictions apply. | ** For non-jumbo mortgages only. ***$500 towards closing costs is for loans above $100,000 between now and August 31, 2019.
                           ]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  ]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ 19th Annual Meeting & Board Elections
]]></page><page Index="5" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ 2019 PFCU Academic Scholarship Awards
]]></page><page Index="6" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Credit union members get $100 per line in cash rewards for every new line activated with Sprint® — and, for a limited time, this offer is available on UNLIMITED lines. Plus, you’ll receive $100 in loyalty cash rewards every year.
Sign up today to enjoy the benefits of credit union membership with Sprint’s best Credit Union Member Cash Rewards offer EVER!
1. Add a line to your new or existing Sprint account and mention you’re a credit union member.
2. Register at LoveMyCreditUnion.org/Paul
3. Cash rewards will be directly deposited into your credit union account within six to
eight weeks.
 Already a Sprint customer?
Register now to receive a $100 loyalty cash reward every year starting one year after registration.
Get Cash Rewards
Take advantage of this limited time offer today! Visit LoveMyCreditUnion.org/Paul to learn more.
KEEP YOUR HOUSE SAFE WHILE YOU’RE AWAY
Headed away to play this summer?
Here are 5 quick tips to keep your home safe while you’re gone so you can really enjoy your stay!
1. Check all doors and windows before you leave to ensure they’re locked up tight. Also reinforce sliding doors at the base of the doors (or windows) with a broom, yardstick, or other block.
2. Ask a friend or neighbor to help out. They can pick up your mail or packages until your return from your trip.
3. Make it look like someone is at home. Set timers to turn your lights on and off and leave a car parked in your driveway if possible.
4. Don’t tell criminals you’re leaving by broadcasting your absence on social media. You can still post those great photos as soon as you return. You don’t want to spend your vacay on your phone anyway!
5. Install cameras for real peace of mind. Smart home products can make your life much safer and your vacation much sweeter!
    1-877-PFCU4YOU (732-8496) www.platinumfcu.org Info@platinumfcu.org
Board of Directors
Rahim Asani Chairman
Amin Premjee Vice Chairman
Ali Jamal Secretary
Fazal Manji Treasurer
Karim Kaisani Director-Supervisory Committee
Shahina Punjani Director-Marketing
Shereza Tajuddin Director-Recovery
Moyees Merchant Director-Outreach
Mansoor Wadasariya Director
Holiday Closings
Independence Day
Thursday, July 4, 2019
Imamat Day
Closing Early, Thursday, July 11, 2019
Labor Day
Monday, September 2, 2019
             We have more than 5,000 shared branch locations. Call us or visit our website to find one near you
Federally insured by NCUA
  Assets: Loans: Members:
May 2019 $116,484,910 $86,447,869 9,299
February 2019 $112,075,178 $84,501,115 9,114
November 2018 $104,840,303 $83,204,076 8973
August 2018 $101,218,652 $79,460,475 9,039
]]></page></pages></Search>