<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="4"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Dear Members:
On behalf of the entire Team at Platinum Federal Credit Union (PFCU), I would like to wish you and your family a Happy New Year. Thank you for your participation and being an ambassador of the credit union.
Mashallah! Platinum Federal Credit Union (PFCU) has had a great year. Alhamdulillah! We grew in all areas
i.e. Assets, Loans, Deposits, Membership, employees, etc. Membership, Deposit, Loan, Account and Net Worth growth all have been moving in the right direction as we continue our journey towards helping more members of our Ismaili Community and be the Partners in your Progress.
In the last quarter of 2018 we re-launched the Memphis Virtual branch and it was well received by the members of our community in Memphis, TN. We would like to thank the National and SE EPB as well as the SE council for their support and help to create awareness of the products and services offered by PFCU to community members in the Memphis, TN area.
I would like to thank members who came to AKF Walk held at the beautiful Stone Mountain Park and walked under the PFCU banner. We are proud to continue our support and contributions to the larger community efforts like Aga Khan Foundation, Hurricane Michael Relief Fund and AKEPB
Financial Literacy & Planning Program. We are also gearing up to launch the 2019 PFCU Academic Scholarship Program that has grown from $5,000 in 2011 to $105,000 in 2018.
We are working on a new plastic card design for our VISA® Platinum Credit Card and plan to launch our new mobile first website in 2019. Please visit the existing website at www.platinumfcu.org or www.Platinum.CreditUnion to obtain the latest information on products, services, rates, financial literacy, etc.
Several members took advantage of the CD special we ran in September and October for 13 and 38 months with favorable options. We will continue to run specials for various products in 2019. Subscribe to receive the PFCU email specials and newsletters to ensure you are the first to know about them.
I would like to thank you again for your continued support
as both members and ambassadors. You, our ambassadors, have proven to spread the word of the products and services offered by PFCU. With your participation and the hard work by our staff and volunteers, we can keep achieving milestones and help more members of our community.
    Sincerely,
Rahim Asani
Rahim Asani Chairman
]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ ]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Checking accounts that check all the right boxes!
At PFCU, we offer several Personal and Business Checking Accounts specifically designed to fit any need you have. Our checking accounts check all the right boxes! Check out which
one is right for you and open it today!
]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ PFCU Election Watch!
Platinum Federal Credit Union is soliciting members to be elected to the PFCU Board of Directors for 2019 – 2022. We would like to request members who have financial exper- tise, banking experience or other core skills to please call the Nominating Committee Chairman, Mr. Karim Kaisani at (404) 787-2536 or email KarimK@PlatinumFCU.org.
Qualified members can run for election as part of the nomination slate or can submit a petition signed by 1% of the membership (i.e. 90 mem- bers of Platinum Federal Credit Union). Inter- ested members should submit their completed
application (available at the credit union), state- ment of qualifications and biographical data to:
Platinum Federal Credit Union
Attn: Nominating Committee Chairman 2035 Sugarloaf Parkway
Duluth, GA 30097
All applications must be submitted no later than February 15, 2019.
Applicants should obtain the requirements of the position and other details from the credit union office.
   Members have saved nearly $2 billion with Love My Credit Union® Rewards!
                         Get more from your credit union membership at LoveMyCreditUnion.org
                            1-877-PFCU4YOU (732-8496) www.platinumfcu.org Info@platinumfcu.org
Board of Directors
Rahim Asani Chairman
Nooruddin Mithani Vice Chairman
Amin Premjee Secretary
Fazal Manji Treasurer
Ali Jamal Director - HR
Karim Kaisani
Director – Supervisory Committee
Amyn Abdulla Director – Marketing
Mushtaq Kamruddin Director – Recovery
Moyees Merchant Director – Outreach
Holiday Closings
New Year’s Day Tuesday, January 1
Martin Luther King, Jr. Day: Monday, January 21
President’s Day: Monday, February 18
Early Closing:
Navroz Mubarak Thursday, March 21
We have more than 5,000 shared branch locations. Call us or visit our website to find one near you
Federally insured by NCUA
               Assets: Loans: Members:
November 2018 $104,840,303 $83,204,076 8973
August 2018 $101,218,652 $79,460,475 9,039
May 2018 $100,512,221 $77,432,859 8,880
February 2018 $98,365,062 $72,977,254 8,731
]]></page></pages></Search>